http://www.great-chicago-italian-recipes.com/policy.html

HomeShut Up and MangiaItalian FoodMia Cucina PazzoItalian AncestryGreat ChefsNew ContestItalian Food BlogRestaurant ReviewYour ReviewsTips and InfoHealthy RecipesAppetizer RecipesSoup RecipesSalad RecipesBread RecipesVegetable RecipesPasta RecipesPoultry RecipesBeef RecipesPork RecipesVeal RecipesLamb RecipesSeafood RecipesPizza RecipesCooking for KidsItalian CheeseItalian WinesDessert RecipesCoffee and EspressoItalian MusicFood GlossaryAbout the CookSitemapShare This SiteContact UsPrivacy PolicyDisclaimerYour Italian RecipesArchived MenusItalian Experiance
[?]Subscribe To This Site
Great Chicago Italian Recipes Privacy Policy
We recognize that your privacy is important. This document outlines the types of personal information we receive and collect when you use Great Chicago Italian Recipes.com, as well as some of the steps we take to safeguard information. We hope this will help you make an informed decision about sharing personal information with us.
Great Chicago Italian Recipes.com strives to maintain the highest standards of decency, fairness and integrity in all our operations. Likewise, we are dedicated to protecting our customers', consumers' and online visitors' privacy on our website.
Personal Information
Great Chicago Italian recipes.com collects personally identifiable information from the visitors to our website only on a voluntary basis. Personal information collected on a voluntary basis may include name, postal address, email address, company name and telephone number.
This information is collected if you request information from us, participate in a contest or sweepstakes, and sign
up to join our email list or request some other service or information from us. The information collected is internally
reviewed, used to improve the content of our website, notify
our visitors of updates, and respond to visitor inquiries.
Once information is reviewed, it is discarded or stored in
our files. If we make material changes in the collection of
personally identifiable information we will inform you by placing a notice on our site. Personal information received from any visitor will be used only for internal purposes and will not be sold or provided to third parties.
Use of Cookies and Web Beacons
We may use cookies to help you personalize your online experience. Cookies are identifiers that are transferred to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser to
enable our systems to recognize your browser. The purpose of
a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to
a specific page. For example, if you personalize the sites pages, or register with any of our site's services, a cookie enables (website/company name) to recall your specific information on subsequent visits.
You have the ability to accept or decline cookies by modifying your Web browser; however, if you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the site.
A web beacon is a transparent image file used to monitor your journey around a single website or collection of sites. They are also referred to as web bugs and are commonly used by sites that hire third-party services to monitor traffic. They may be used in association with cookies to understand how visitors interact with the pages and content on the pages of a web site.
Advertising
Some of our advertisers occasionally serve you cookies as well. We do not have control over cookies placed by advertisers. We may use advertising service vendors to help present advertisements on the website, one of which is gourmetads.com. These vendors may use cookies, web beacons, or similar technologies to serve you advertisements tailored to interests you have shown by browsing on this and other sites you have visited, to determine whether you have seen a particular advertisement before and to avoid sending you duplicate advertisements. In doing so, these vendors may collect non-personal data such as your browser type, your operating system, Web pages visited, time of visits, content viewed, ads viewed, and other clickstream data. The use of cookies, web beacons, or similar technologies by these advertising service vendors is subject to their own privacy policies, not ours, and Service Provider disclaims all liability in connection therewith.
Browsers can be set to accept or reject cookies or notify you when a cookie is being sent. Privacy software can be used to override web beacons. Taking either of these actions shouldn't cause a problem with our site, should you so choose.
Opt Out
For information about opting out of Gourmet Ads and ad serving partners please visit
Gourmet Ads Privacy Policy
Children's Online Privacy Protection Act
This website is directed to adults; it is not directed to children under the age of 13. We operate our site in compliance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act, and will not knowingly collect or use personal information from anyone under 13 years of age.
Non-Personal Information
In some cases, we may collect information about you that is not personally identifiable. We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users' movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole.
The information collected is used solely for internal review and not shared with other organizations for commercial purposes.
Release of Information
If Great Chicago Italian Recipes.com is sold, the information we have obtained from you through your voluntary participation in our site may transfer to the new owner as a part of the sale in order that the service being provided to you may continue. In that event, you will receive notice through our website of that change in control and practices, and we will make reasonable efforts to ensure that the purchaser honors any opt-out requests you might make of us.
How You Can Correct or Remove Information
We provide this privacy policy as a statement to you of our commitment to protect your personal information. If you have submitted personal information through our website and would like that information deleted from our records or would like to update or correct that information, please click on this link and/or use our Contact Us page.
Updates and Effective Date
Great Chicago Italian Recipes.com reserves the right to make changes in this policy. If there is a material change in our privacy practices, we will indicate on our site that our privacy practices have changed and provide a link to the new privacy policy. We encourage you to periodically review this policy so that you will know what information we collect and how we use it.
Agreeing to Terms
If you do not agree to Great-Chicago-Italian-recipes.com’s Privacy Policy as posted here on this website, please do not use this site or any services offered by this site.
Your use of this site indicates acceptance of this privacy policy.
Don't forget to click on the logo below and subscribe to myNEW NEWSLETTER
That's a discovery! That's Italian! That'sGreat Chicago Italian Recipes.com
Copyright 2017 Great Chicago Italian Recipes.com All Rights Reserved
SBI!
